<tools>
  <tool>
    <name>autoconf</name>
    <desc>
      Creates a script which analyzes the target for any needed information and
      provides that information to the program by using macros.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Build simplification</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool>
    <name>automake</name>
    <desc>
      Creates a make file which uses the information autoconf provided to
      perform potentially complex build processes using a very simple set of
      make targets.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Build simplification</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool>
    <name>doxygen</name>
    <desc>
      Generates easy-to-read documentation in a variety of formats by using
      javadoc-style docblocks placed throughout the code.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Documentation simplification</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool>
    <name>dejagnu</name>
    <desc>
      Centralized testing suite that runs collections of tests written in
      expect, but can also be used for unit testing.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Test automation and unification</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool>
    <name>valgrind</name>
    <desc>
      Analyzes memory usage for potential memory leaks, heap overflows, and
      many other memory-related performance, stability, and security problems.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Robust memory analysis</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool>
    <name>gcov</name>
    <desc>
      Simple code coverage tool that requires certain GCC flags.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Test sufficiency analysis</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool>
    <name>gprof</name>
    <desc>
      A good code profiling tool that requires certain GCC flags.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Runtime performance analysis</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool arguable="yes">
    <name>libtool</name>
    <desc>
      A tool that greatly simplifies the process of creating a shared library
      when combined with automake.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Build simplification (in we're building a library)</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool>
    <name>pkg-config</name>
    <desc>
      A tool which generates a metadata file which describes the package, any
      configuration options, any compiler flags, and any other data that would
      be helpful to another application being built or installed that would
      like to use this application as a dependency.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Build simplification for any future dependent software</benefit>
  </tool>
  <tool arguable="yes">
    <name>gettext</name>
    <desc>
      A library and toolset that greatly simplifies the process of adding
      internationalization support to an application.
    </desc>
    <benefit>Internationalization support and simplification</benefit>
  </tool>
</tools>
<libs>
  <lib>
    <name>libmicrohttpd</name>
    <desc>
      Library for adding a minimal HTTPD server to a C program.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Serving the site API, mobile API, and web frontend</purpose>
  </lib>
  <lib>
    <name>OpenSSL</name>
    <desc>
      Library for working with SSL connections and some related tasks.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Encryption and decryption, SSL tunnels for libmicrohttpd</purpose>
  </lib>
  <lib>
    <name>cURL</name>
    <desc>
      Library for making HTTP client calls.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Communicating with AWS API, maybe Google and Apple also</purpose>
  </lib>
  <lib arguable="yes">
    <name>gettext</name>
    <desc>
      A library and toolset that greatly simplifies the process of adding
      internationalization support to an application.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Internationalization support and simplification</purpose>
  </lib>
</libs>
<services>
  <service>
    <name>EC2</name>
    <desc>
      Amazon Web Services Elastic Compute Cloud, a cloud server provider.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Running the program</purpose>
  </service>
  <service>
    <name>DynamoDB</name>
    <desc>
      Amazon Web Services DynamoDB, a fast and scalable key-value store.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Long-term storage of connection attempts</purpose>
  </service>
  <service>
    <name>EBS</name>
    <desc>
      Amazon Web Services Elastic Block Store, a persistent filesystem for EC2.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Short-term storage of logs</purpose>
  </service>
  <service>
    <name>S3</name>
    <desc>
      Amazon Web Services Simple Storage Server, a simple and cheap filesystem.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Long-term storage of log summaries and site icons</purpose>
  </service>
  <service>
    <name>ElastiCache</name>
    <desc>
      Amazon Web Services ElastiCache, an in-memory cache system.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Short-term storage of requests, icons, keys, etc.</purpose>
  </service>
  <service>
    <name>RDB</name>
    <desc>
      Amazon Web Services Relational DataBase, a traditional database.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Long-term storage of user and site metadata</purpose>
  </service>
  <service>
    <name>Glacier</name>
    <desc>
      Amazon Web Services Glacier, a very cheap long-term data vault.
    </desc>
    <purpose>Backups, long-term storage of verbose logs</purpose>
  </service>
</services>
